Live unlimited and infinite adventures, the only limit is your imagination.
AIdventure is a text adventure game with an AI as a storyteller.
What does it mean ?
It means you can live any adventure in the way you want !
Play as a scientist discovering ancient horrors.
Be a nobody waking up, NAKED, in a tube after the apocalypse.
Try to survive a zombie apocalypse.
(or be the zombie !)
YOU choose where the story goes, the AI will always adapt to all your choices.
YOU are the HERO, and sometimes the ZERO, of your OWN fiction.
Play as Stalin ! And invade Poland !
(We said not Stalin !)
Alright !
Play as Mussolini ! And invade Albania !
(Stop saying shit, follow the script !)
Alright !
Live epic adventures !
Or, just help your neighbour with her plumbing problems.
Wink, wink. (What ? Oh, fuck off...)
AH, AH !
AIdventure ! No rules, no censorship !
The only limit is your imagination, not someone else's !